what's going on everybody welcome to the
这是怎么回事大家 欢迎
sixth TV basics tutorial video in this
第六部 电视基础教程视频在 这
video what we're gonna be talking about
视频我们会 谈论什么
is the float layout so this is another
是浮动布局，所以这是另一个
version of a layout now as we can see
现在我们可以看到布局的版本
this layout is is fairly responsive you
这种布局是 相当敏感的 你
know we can move things around at least
知道我们至少可以移动
and the buttons are somewhat placed
并且按钮有点放置
decently but not the greatest and you
体面， 但不是最伟大的 ，你
can do stuff like this right and and you
可以做这样的事情和你一样
you can conceive there are some layouts
你可以想象有一些布局
that are some reasons why you wouldn't
这是一些原因， 你不会
want this layout so I'm going to show
想要这个布局，所以我要 展示
one more layout and that's going to be
多一个布局，这 将是
the float layout so the idea of the
浮动布局，使的想法
float layout is that you can kind of
浮动布局是你可以种的
dynamically size and place things so I
动态地调整大小和放置事物
don't know stuff like this doesn't
不知道这样的东西 没有
really happen so anyway let's go ahead
无论如何真的发生，让我们继续前进
and close this and talk about that so
并关闭它并谈论 这一点
for me I'm going to make some changes
对我来说，我会做一些改变
again this will be my kv file for I'm
再次，这将是我的 kv文件，因为我是
already regretting not keeping these the
已经很遗憾没有保留这些
same number as the video but that's okay
与 视频 数量相同 ， 但没关系
so case 6 and this one's already saved
所以情况 6和这个已经保存了
as for cool so I'm gonna save that ok
至于酷， 所以我会保存 好的
now we're ready to go ahead and get
现在我们已经准备好 继续前进，得到
started so I'm going to the only thing I
开始，所以我要去 我唯一
would get rid of here let's see four
会摆脱这里让我们看看四个
button will be size so we'll keep the
按钮的大小将会保持不变
font size as 44 now I mean you might
字体大小为44现在我的意思是你可能
want to change that something more
想要改变更多的东西
dynamic later on but we'll keep the font
稍后动态，但我们会保留字体
size as 40 and we'll talk about the
大小为40，我们将谈论
other stuff later but then we'll just
其他的东西，但后来我们会
delete this so currently we'll just have
删除这个，所以目前我们只会有
a you know this button definition so
你知道这个按钮的定义如此
we'll save that and no longer do we need
我们会保存它，不再需要
our widgets class we're going to get rid
我们的小部件类我们要 摆脱
of that for now we want to keep
现在我们想保留
everything as simple as possible so you
一切尽可能简单 ， 所以你
can kind of see the required connections
可以看到所需的连接
and nothing more
也没有更多
so we're also going to get getting learn
所以我们也将 得到越来越学习
to speak so here at a widget we don't
至所以在这里说，在 一个小窗口，我们不
need that anymore and in fact we aren't
需要再这样了 。事实上，我们都没有
even going to need label we're just
即使需要标签，我们也是
going to have key v-app import app and
将有关键的V  - 应用程序导入应用程序和
then one more thing we're going to now
那么我们现在要做的 还有一件事
say
说
from TV Dai UI x dot flow layout import
从电视戴UI x点流程布局导入
capital F float capital L layout now we
大写F浮动资本L现在我们布局
deleted our widgets class so we can't
删除我们的小部件类，所以我们不能
use that anymore so we have to use float
再次使用，所以我们必须使用浮点数
layout so now our simple app is just
所以现在我们的简单应用就是布局
gonna return float layout now that's
现在 要返回 浮动布局
really nothing it should run still but
真的没什么 它应该 仍然 运行， 但
there's really nothing to our float
我们的浮动确实没有什么
layout it's just a blank screen at the
布局它只是一个空白的屏幕
moment whoops
一会儿哎哟
so I guess hold it here yes so how do we
所以我想 在这里举行 是的，所以我们如何
add this float layout well all we need
我们需要添加这个浮动布局
to do is you know these parent and
要做的是你知道这些家长和
children so now we can specify this
孩子们，现在我们可以指定这一点
parent class that we have which is float
父类，我们有它是浮动的
layout so let's just go ahead and do
所以让我们继续前进吧
that so add our little tags for the
那 为我们 添加 我们的小标签
parent and this is float layout
父母，这是浮动布局
don't forget your colon it's really easy
不要忘记你的冒号，这很容易
for you Python folk 1 2 3 4 and now
为你 蟒民间 1 2 3 4和 现在
we're ready to kind of define some
我们准备好定义一些
things about the float layout now for me
关于浮动布局现在对我来说
all I say that we're going to have two
我只说我们会有两个
buttons so we're gonna have a button
按钮，所以我们会有一个按钮
here and a button here now we can add
在这里， 现在我们可以添加 一个按钮
some text to our buttons so 1 2 3 4 and
一些文字给 我们的 按钮如此1 2 3 4 和
we'll say text is a key B and then down
我们会说文本是关键B然后关闭
here or - oops
这里或 - 哎呀
1 2 3 4 texts will be again TV so now
1个2 3 4文本将再次电视机 所以现在
we've got two buttons with text we've
我们有两个 带有文字的 按钮
got font size and color but we don't
有字体大小和颜色， 但我们 没有
have the buttons sighs now one of the
有按钮叹息现在的其中 之一
kind of things about our float layout
有关我们的浮动布局的一些事情
that's going to be cool is that we can
我们可以做到这一点很酷
use a dynamic size with some hinting and
使用一些动态大小暗示和
we quite literally the parameter for
我们完全是字面上 的参数
this is size underscore hint and we want
这 是大小下划线提示 ，我们想要
to say our size hint will say is point
说我们的尺寸暗示会说是重点
four now we're going to say 0.3 I'll
四我们现在 要说 0.3我会的
show you I think the best thing is to
告诉你我认为最好的事情是
kind of write it out and then show you
有点写 出来然后告诉你
how everything affects things but this
除了这一点，一切事物 如何 影响事物
is basically 0.3 of the wit so in fact
事实上，这个机智基本上是0.3
let's do 0.25 so it's 1/4 of the X and
让我们做0.25，因此它是X和的1/4
then of the Y we're going to say zero
那么我们要说的是 零
point
点
oh I guess why actually let's do point
哦，我猜为什么我们要做点
okay
好的
we'll play with these later anyway um so
无论如何，我们都会和他们一起玩
this is our button so now this is the
这 是我们的按钮，所以现在 是这样 的
like the parent information so this
像这样 这样 的家长信息
stuff is already being applied to these
东西已经被应用 到这些
okay the only thing that's different is
没关系， 唯一不同的是
the text which I guess isn't different
我猜想的文字并没有什么不同
some make this tutorials I don't know
有些使这个教程我不知道
why row TV twice
为什么排列电视两次
wasn't thinking I guess so we've got
没有想到 我想我们有
text text and now the only other thing
文本文本和现在唯一的其他东西
that we really need to do is the
我们真的需要 做的是
position of the button so for position
位置的按钮位置
it's kind of like size hint and the term
它有点像大小提示和术语
here is going to be posts underscore
这里将是 帖子的下划线
hence : and this is going to actually be
因此 ：这 是要 实际上是
like a dictionary okay so you've got
像一本字典好，所以你 有
your key and your value and the key can
你的钥匙 和你的 价值和钥匙可以
be a lot of things you've got X Y
是很多 你有XY 的东西
left/right up/down or top bottom press
左/右上/下或顶部按下
I'm sorry X Y left right top bottom
对不起XY左右上方
sorry don't mean to confuse anyone so in
对不起， 并不意味着 混淆 这样 的人 在
each one kind of has a slightly
每一种都有一点点
different idea to it but anyway well
不同的想法 ，但无论如何
we'll use them all or will try to
我们将全部使用它们或将 尝试使用它们
anyways at least one from each of
反正每个至少有一个
dichotomy so we're going to say the X X
二分法， 所以我们要说XX
will be and actually this needs to be in
将是，实际上这需要 在
quotes so X : and we're going to say X
引用 X：我们会 说 X
will be just 0 so this will be the 0
将只是0，所以 这将 是 0
with or the no X okay so 0 basically
基本上 没有 X没问题
these values all of them are going to be
这些价值观都将成为现实
between 0 and they'll be somewhere
在0之间， 他们会在某个地方
between 0 and 1 1 being full complete 0
在0 和11之间是完整的0
being none so if x is 0 that should make
如果x是0， 应该是没有的
total sense to you where where is X 0
对你来说总的意义在哪里是X 0
well it that means left all completely
那么这意味着完全离开
left then now we need some sort of Y
现在我们需要某种Y.
definition now we could we could
现在我们可以做到这一点
literally say Y and we say Y is 0 or we
从字面上说Y，我们说Y 是0或我们
can say I think it's lower case T top
可以说我认为它是小写 字母T top
top but is top like top the question
顶部，但顶部像顶部的问题
it's like almost like a degree of tapas
它就像一个小吃一样
so if we say top 0 this means it has 0
所以如果我们说顶部0 这 意味着它有 0
degrees of tapas so actually top 0 would
实际上顶级0的西班牙小吃的程度
be bottom ok so we're going to say
最后 确定，所以我们要说
one so this key B button needs to be or
一个所以这个关键的B按钮需要或
will be according to the hints the top
将根据提示顶部
left now that's not really that special
现在离开这并不是那么特别
we could have done that really easily
我们 可以 很容易地 做到 这一点
but this button is where it's going to
但是这个按钮就是它要去 的地方
really shine so now we will do a posts
真的很闪耀， 所以现在我们 会做一个帖子
underscore hint and again this time
下划线提示 ，这次又一次
we'll say instead of X we'll use a
我们会说，而不是 X我们将使用一个
different one we'll say right and this
不同的一个 ，我们会说 的权利，这
is so our degree of rightness so if we
那么我们的正确性的程度，所以如果我们
wanted a button to be completely right
想要一个按钮是完全正确的
what degree of rightness would we have
我们有 什么样的正确性
complete full rightness one then we'll
完全正确， 然后 我们会
have another variable here and we'll say
在 这里 有另一个变量 ，我们会说
for now I will just the top one again
现在我会 再次登顶
and let's just make ups one and let's
让我们 做 一个让我们来
make sure everything works up to this
确保一切正常到 这
point so we haven't really tested
所以我们还没有真正测试过
anything right so now you've got key V
任何事情都是对的，所以现在你已经有了关键的V
and you've got tutorials and then what
你有教程，然后是什么
we can do is we can kind of move
我们能做的是我们可以有所动作
everything around okay and you can see
一切都好， 你可以看到
that a couple of things are happening
有几 件事情正在发生
not only are the buttons moving they're
不仅 是按钮移动他们
changing in size so we could even
改变的大小， 所以我们 甚至 可以
although the text is going to run over
尽管文本将会结束
but we could do this and you'll see that
但我们可以做到这一点，你会看到
the buttons themselves at least will not
按钮本身至少不会
run into each other so this would be an
碰上 对方 因此这将是一个
example of having you know many
你知道很多的 例子
different screen resolutions yet
不同的屏幕分辨率 呢
everything still fits and you've got no
一切仍然 适合， 你没有
run over so the float layout pretty much
几乎所有的浮动布局运行
can allow you to stop things from
可以让你阻止事情发生
running over each other so long as
只要跑过对方
you're using the hints right because we
你正在使用提示，因为我们
can still make text run over well I'm
仍然可以让文本顺利运行
going to do it there we go okay you can
在那里我们可以做到
make text run over each other now um
使文本现在运行在彼此之上
that's basically it
基本上就是这样
but let's just really solidify what
但让我们真正巩固什么
we're what we're seeing here so let's
我们就是我们在这里看到的，所以让我们来看看
leave well now let's move TV so we're
现在保持良好， 让我们移动 电视，让我们
going to say top whatever we'll say
要说 顶部无论 我们会说
instead of one zero point five so this
而不是一个零点五， 所以这个
will be half topping this right so this
这将是一半这个权利
can get kind of confusing because now
因为现在可能会有点 混乱
when we say top is 0.5 it almost looks
当我们说top是0.5时，它几乎看起来像
like this keavy element right
像这个重磅元素的权利
like here's the top 0.5 is here and now
像这里现在是最高的0.5
it's beginning to look like this element
它开始看起来 像这个元素
here is being treated as if it's moving
这里正在被视为 移动
around by the top-left corner right
在左上角的右边
because this marks 50% not this okay so
因为这标志着 50％不是这样 好
I can get pretty confusing pretty fast
我可以相当快地相当困惑
or pretty challenging at least
或者至少很有挑战性
especially because this so now this
尤其是因为现在这个
application could in theory be almost
应用在理论上可能差不多
dictated by either the bottom left or
由左下角或左下角指定
the top left that kind of sucks I could
那个左上角那种 我可以 吮吸的东西
get really confusing really fast but I
真的让我感到非常困惑，但我
like the idea that you can orient things
就像你可以定位东西的想法一样
by different different values but let's
通过不同的值， 但让我们
try now Y 0.5 uh what I must have hit f5
现在试试Y 0.5呃 我必须击中F5
on the TV okay let's drive over done
在电视上好吧， 让我们继续完成
right so now and you can see how this is
现在就是这样，你可以看到这是怎么回事
by the Y element you know half and this
由Y元素你知道一半和这个
is illustrating how Y is indeed
正在说明Y的确是如此
referencing the bottom left because this
因为这个，引用左下角
marks the halfway mark right down here
这里 标志着过半 降 权
this of course doesn't we can see this
这当然不能 看到这一点
very easily visually so that's kind of
非常容易看到，所以这是一种
corresponding to the rest of keavy worst
对应于最糟糕的其余部分
top does it but then what if we said
顶部做它，但如果我们说，然后呢
okay we come over here and we said
好吧，我们过来了 ，我们说
bottom so the degree of bottom miss
底部如此底部的失误程度
there but 0.5 right okay so anyway you
无论如何，只要 0.5 就可以
can imagine that this can get pretty
可以想象 这可以变得漂亮
confusing pretty fast especially like
混乱相当快， 特别喜欢
you can you start playing with these
你可以开始玩这些
like say bottom is zero and then you're
就像说底部是零，然后你是
expecting right like my expectation of
期望像我的期望一样
bottom equals zero would be actually top
底部等于零实际上是最高的
right like it would be zero degrees of
就像它会是零度
bottomless but anyway I the reason why
深不见底，但无论如何，我之所以
that's occurring I believe anyways would
我相信无论如何 会 发生 这种情况
be is because the degree of bottom is to
是因为底部的程度是
zero but since everything starts at zero
零但是 因为一切从零开始
zero
零
it remains at the bottom okay so I think
它仍然在底部好， 所以我 认为
that's what's happening here and that
这就是这里和那发生的事情
would be why maybe you would say why you
这就是为什么你会说为什么你
would I it's hard because it just
我会很难，因为它只是
depends on which way you've always
取决于你总是以哪种方式
you've been oriented
你已经被定位
your program as far as like where you
你的程序就 好像你在那里
want to you know what words you might
希望你知道你可能会说些什么
want to use but anyway keep it in mind
想要使用， 但无论如何要记住它
that it's going to be somewhat confusing
这将 是 有些 混乱
sometimes but you've got all of these
有时候， 但 你已经掌握了所有 这些
values and I think the best way to
价值观，我认为 最好的办法
envision these values is in Ness right
设想这些价值观在尼斯是正确的
so this is X Ness - top Ness rightness
所以这就是X尼斯 - 尼斯的正确性
but you can do stuff like you know
但你可以 像你知道的那样 做 东西
degrees like this like right 0.3 for
度这样 如 右图0.3
example right let's do 0.5 for the one
例如正确的，让我们对一个做0.5
that's over some and we can run that and
这是关于一些，我们可以运行和
you can see here that it's always going
你可以在这里看到它 总是会发生的
to start at about you know 30% so you
开始在你知道 30％，所以你
can move the window all you want and you
可以移动你想要 的窗口 和你
pretty much can always be comfortable as
几乎总是可以舒适的
far as where the button will be again
就像按钮将再次出现的位置一样
the text is not meshing with us but we
文字不与我们啮合， 但我们
can work on that as well so anyway
可以对工作，以及 因此， 无论如何
that's going to be it for the float
这将是 浮动的
layout and all that hopefully that made
布局和希望所做的一切
sense
感
the first time I saw float layout and
我第一次看到浮动布局和
really still I have to think about it
真的还是要考虑一下
when I'm inputting these values because
当我输入这些值时，因为
you just first of all they've already
你只是首先他们已经
flipped you know where the zero zero is
翻转你知道 零零点 在哪里
on you and then you've got these degrees
在你身上，然后你有了这些学位
of these values that you can input and
这些值，你可以 输入
it gives you a lot of dynamic nests and
它给你很多动态的 巢和
stuff like that but I can be confusing
这样的东西，但我可以混淆
so anyway but you can always pretty much
所以 无论如何，但你总能非常
get away with using x and y but you
脱离使用x和y，但你
should probably know about these as well
或许应该知道 这些，以及
anyways that's it for this tutorial I
无论如何，这是这个 教程我
have any questions or comments please
有任何问题或意见，请
feel free to leave them below otherwise
随意离开他们 ，否则 以下
as always thanks for watching thanks for
一如既往感谢您收看谢谢
all the support subscriptions until next
所有支持订阅，直到下一个
time
时间